Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Scripts
  - Rock, Roll and Remember
    - Show #94-44/664, Oct 29-30, 1994; Rick Nelson (Box 65)
    - Show #94-45/665, Nov 5-6, 1994; Neil Diamond (Box 65)
    - Show #94-46/666, Nov 12-13, 1994; Monkees (Box 65)
    - Show #94-47/667, Nov 19-20, 1994; Supremes (Box 66)
    - Show #94-48/668, Nov 26-27, 1994; Gene Pitney (Box 66)
    - Show #94-49/669, Dec 3-4, 1994; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 66)
    - Show #94-50/670, Dec 10-11, 1994; Temptations (Box 66)
    - Show #94-51/671, Dec 16-17, 1994; Dave Clark Five (Box 66)
    - Show #94-52/672, Dec 23-24, 1994; Holiday special, part 1 (Box 66)
    - Show #94-53/673, Dec 30, 1994-Jan 1, 1995; Holiday special, part 2 (Box 66)
    - Show #95-01/674, Jan 7-8, 1995; Elvis Presley (Box 66)
    - Show #95-02/675, Jan 14-15, 1995; Sam Cooke (Box 66)
    - Show #95-03/676, Jan 21-22, 1995; Doors/Linda Ronstadt (Box 66)
    - Show #95-04/677, Jan 28-29, 1995; Earth Wind & Fire/Righteous Brothers (Box 66)
    - Show #95-05/678, Feb 4-5, 1995; Elton John (Box 66)
    - Show #95-06/679, Feb 11-12, 1995; John, Paul, George & Ringo (Box 66)
    - Show #95-07/680, Feb 18-19, 1995; Bobby Vee (Box 67)
    - Show #95-08/681, Feb 25-26, 1995; Salute to Girl Groups (Box 67)
    - Show #95-09/682, Mar 4-5, 1995; James Taylor (Box 67)
    - Show #95-10/683, Mar 11-12, 1995; Buddy Holly (Box 67)
    - Show #95-11/684, Mar 18-19, 1995; Jay & the Americans (Box 67)
    - Show #95-12/685, Mar 25-26, 1995; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 67)
    - Show #95-13/686, Apr 1-2, 1995; Four Seasons (Box 67)
    - Show #95-14/687, Apr 8-9, 1995; Three Dog Night (Box 67)
    - Show #95-15/688, Apr 15-16, 1995; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 67)
    - Show #95-16/689, Apr 22-23, 1995; Jan & Dean (Box 67)
    - Show #95-17/690, Apr 29-30, 1995; Grass Roots (Box 67)
    - Show #95-18/691, May 6-7, 1995; Dion (Box 67)
    - Show #95-19/692, May 13-14, 1995; Four Tops (Box 68)
    - Show #95-20/693, May 20-21, 1995; Everly Brothers (Box 68)
    - Show #95-21/694, May 27-28, 1995; Beach Boys (Box 68)
    - Show #95-22/695, Jun 3-4, 1995; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 68)
    - Show #95-23/696, Jun 10-11, 1995; Miracles (Box 68)
    - Show #95-24 to 95-37 [not in collection], Jun 17-18, 1995
    - Show #95-38/711, Sep 23-24, 1995; George Harrison (Box 68)
    - Show #95-39 to 96-50 [not in collection], Sep 30-Oct 1, 1995
    - Show #96-51/776, Dec 21-22, 1996; RRR Christmas Show; cue sheets only (Box 68)
    - Show #96-52/777, Dec 28-29, 1996; Dave Clark Five (Box 68)
    - Show #97-01/778, Jan 4-5, 1997; Marvin Gaye (Box 68)
    - Show #97-02/779, Jan 11-12, 1997; Neil Diamond (Box 68)
    - Show #97-03/780, Jan 18-19, 1997; Dion (Box 68)
    - Show #97-04/781, Jan 25-26, 1997; British Invasion (Box 68)
    - Show #97-05/782, Feb 1-2, 1997; Righteous Brothers & Doors (Box 68)
    - Show #97-06/783, Feb 8-9, 1997; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 69)
    - Show #97-07/784, Feb 15-16, 1997; George Harrison (Box 69)
    - Show #97-08/785, Feb 22-23, 1997; Animals (Box 69)
    - Show #97-09/786, Mar 1-2, 1997; Salute to Vocal Groups (Box 69)
    - Show #97-10/787, Mar 8-9, 1997; Supremes (Box 69)
    - Show #97-11/788, Mar 15-16, 1997; Hollies (Box 69)
    - Show #97-12/789, Mar 22-23, 1997; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 69)
    - Show #97-13/790, Mar 29-30, 1997; Four Tops (Box 69)
    - Show #97-14/791, Apr 5-6, 1997; Jan & Dean (Box 69)
    - Show #97-15/792, Apr 12-13, 1997; Herman’s Hermits (Box 69)
    - Show #97-16/793, Apr 19-20, 1997; Del Shannon (Box 69)
    - Show #97-17/794, Apr 26-27, 1997; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 70)
    - Show #97-18/795, May 3-4, 1997; Neil Sedaka (Box 70)
    - Show #97-19/796, May 10-11, 1997; Four Seasons (Box 70)
    - Show #97-20/797, May 17-18, 1997; Motown Music (Box 70)
    - Show #97-21/798, May 24-25, 1997; Paul McCartney (Box 70)
    - Show #97-22/799, May 31-Jun 1, 1997; Beach Boys (Box 70)
    - Show #97-23/800, Jun 7-8, 1997; Chuck Berry (Box 70)
    - Show #97-24/801, Jun 14-15, 1997; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 70)
    - Show #97-25/802, Jun 22-23, 1997; Ringo Starr (Box 70)
    - Show #97-26/803, Jun 28-29, 1997; Petula Clark (Box 70)
    - Show #97-27/804, Jul 5-6, 1997; All American Hits (Box 70)
    - Show #97-28/805, Jul 12-13, 1997; Miracles (Box 71)
    - Show #97-29/806, Jul 19-20, 1997; Johnny Rivers (Box 71)
    - Show #97-30/807, Jul 26-27, 1997; Temptations (Box 71)
    - Show #97-31/808, Aug 2-3, 1997; Association (Box 71)
    - Show #97-32/809, Aug 9-10, 1997; Rascals (Box 71)
    - Show #97-33/810, Aug 16-17, 1997; Elvis Presley (20th Ann, of death) (Box 71)
    - Show #97-34/811, Aug 23-24, 1997; Donovan (Box 71)
    - Show #97-35/812, Aug 30-31, 1997; Roy Orbison (Box 71)
    - Show #97-36/813, Sep 6-7, 1997; Stevie Wonder (Box 71)
    - Show #97-37/814, Sep 13-14, 1997; Dion and the Belmonts (Box 71)
    - Show #97-38/815, Sep 20-21, 1997; Everly Brothers (Box 71)
    - Show #97-39/816, Sep 27-28, 1997; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 72)
    - Show #97-40/817, Oct 4-5, 1997; Beatles (Box 72)
    - Show #97-41/818, Oct 11-12, 1997; Brenda Lee (Box 72)
    - Show #97-42/819, Oct 18-19, 1997; Salute to Phil Spector (Box 72)
    - Show #97-43/820, Oct 25-26, 1997; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 72)
    - Show #97-44/821, Nov 1-2, 1997; Supremes (Box 72)
    - Show #97-45/822, Nov 8-9, 1997; Jackie Wilson (Box 72)
    - Show #97-46/823, Nov 15-16, 1997; Gene Pitney (Box 72)
    - Show #97-47/824, Nov 22-23, 1997; Kinks (Box 72)
    - Show #97-48/825, Nov 29-30, 1997; Little Richard (Box 72)
    - Show #97-49/826, Dec 6-7, 1997; The Monkees (Box 72)
    - Show #97-50/827, Dec 13-14, 1997; Dave Clark Five (Box 73)
    - Show #97-51/828, Dec 20-21, 1997; RRR Christmas ShowSong list only, no script (Box 73)
    - Show #97-52/829, Dec 27-28, 1997; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 73)
    - Show #98-01/830, Jan 3-4, 1998; Drifters (Box 73)
    - Show #98-02/831, Jan 10-11, 1998; Animals (Box 73)
    - Show #98-03/832, Jan 17-18, 1998; Fifth Dimension (Box 73)
    - Show #98-04/833, Jan 24-25, 1998; Dion (Box 73)
    - Show #98-05/834, Jan 31-Feb 1, 1998; Four Tops (Box 73)
    - Show #98-06/835, Feb 7-8, 1998; Sam Cooke (Box 73)
    - Show #98-07/836, Feb 14-15, 1998; Hollies (Box 73)
    - Show #98-08/837, Feb 21-22, 1998; Bobby Vee (Box 73)
    - Show #98-09/838, Feb 28-Mar 1, 1998; Salute to Dance (Box 73)
    - Show #98-10/839, Mar 7-8, 1998; Marvin Gaye (Box 73)
    - Show #98-11/840, Mar 14-15, 1998; Del Shannon (Box 74)
    - Show #98-12/841, Mar 21-22, 1998; Grass Roots (Box 74)
    - Show #98-13/842, Mar 28-29, 1998; Buddy Holly (Box 74)
    - Show #98-14/843, Apr 4-5, 1998; Jan & Dean (Box 74)
    - Show #98-15/844, Apr 11-12, 1998; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 74)
    - Show #98-16/845, Apr 18-19, 1998; Paul McCartney (Box 74)
    - Show #98-17/846, Apr 25-26, 1998; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 74)
    - Show #98-18/847, May 2-3, 1998; Four Seasons (Box 74)
    - Show #98-19/848, May 9-10, 1998; Chuck Berry (Box 74)
    - Show #98-20/849, May 16-17, 1998; Lesley Gore (Box 74)
    - Show #98-21/850, May 23-24, 1998; Beach Boys (Box 74)
    - Show #98-22/851, May 30-31, 1998; Salute to Girl Groups (Box 75)
    - Show #98-23/852, Jun 6-7, 1998; Gene Pitney (Box 75)
    - Show #98-24/853, Jun 13-14, 1998; Gary Lewis & the Playboys (Box 75)
    - Show #98-25/854, Jun 20-21, 1998; Petula Clark (Box 75)
    - Show #98-26/855, Jun 27-28, 1998; Ray Charles (Box 75)
    - Show #98-27/856, Jul 4-5, 1998; Hal Blaine (Box 75)
    - Show #98-28/857, Jul 11-12, 1998; Temptations (Box 75)
    - Show #98-29/858, Jul 18-19, 1998; Johnny Rivers (Box 75)
    - Show #98-30/859, Jul 25-26, 1998; Rascals (Box 75)
    - Show #98-31/860, Aug 1-2, 1998; Salute to Vocal Groups (Box 75)
    - Show #98-32/861, Aug 8-9, 1998; Herman’s Hermits (Box 75)
    - Show #98-33/862, Aug 15-16, 1998; Miracles (Box 75)
    - Show #98-34/863, Aug 22-23, 1998; Roy Orbison (Box 76)
    - Show #98-35/864, Aug 29-30, 1998; Neil Diamond (Box 76)
    - Show #98-36/865, Sep 5-6, 1998; Buddy Holly (Box 76)
    - Show #98-37/866, Sep 12-13, 1998; Ben E. King (Box 76)
    - Show #98-38/867, Sep 19-20, 1998; Bobby Darin (Box 76)
    - Show #98-39/868, Sep 26-27, 1998; John Lennon (Box 76)
    - Show #98-40/869, Oct 3-4, 1998; Jackie Wilson (Box 76)
    - Show #98-41/870, Oct 10-11, 1998; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 76)
    - Show #98-42/871, Oct 17-18, 1998; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 76)
    - Show #98-43/872, Oct 24-25, 1998; Four Tops (Box 76)
    - Show #98-44/873, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1998; Animals (Box 76)
    - Show #98-45/874, Nov 7-8, 1998; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 76)
    - Show #98-46/875, Nov 14-15, 1998; Mamas & the Papas (Box 77)
    - Show #98-47/876, Nov 21-22, 1998; British Invasion (Box 77)
    - Show #98-48/877, Nov 29-30, 1998; Turtles (Box 77)
    - Show #98-49/878, Dec 5-6, 1998; George Harrison (Box 77)
    - Show #98-50/879, Dec 12-13, 1998; Supremes (Box 77)
    - Show #98-51/880 [not in collection], Dec 19-20, 1998; RRR Christmas Show
    - Show #98-52/881, Dec 26-27, 1998; Dave Clark Five (Box 77)
    - Show #99-01/882 [not in collection], Jan 2-3, 1999; Drifters
    - Show #99-02/883, Jan 9-10, 1999; Fifth Dimension (Box 77)
    - Show #99-03/884, Jan 16-17, 1999; Dion (Box 77)
    - Show #99-04/885, Jan 23-24, 1999; Paul Revere & the Raiders (Box 77)
    - Show #99-05/886, Jan 30-31, 1999; Del Shannon (Box 77)
    - Show #99-06/887, Feb 6-7, 1999; Songs that carried messages (Box 77)
    - Show #99-07/888, Feb 13-14, 1999; Bobby Vee (Box 77)
    - Show #99-08/889, Feb 20-21, 1999; Kinks (Box 78)
    - Show #99-09/890, Feb 27-28, 1999; Stevie Wonder (Box 78)
    - Show #99-10/891 [not in collection], Mar 6-7, 1999; Gene Pitney
    - Show #99-11/892, Mar 13-14, 1999; Everly Brothers (Box 78)
    - Show #99-12/893, Mar 20-21, 1999; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 78)
    - Show #99-13/894, Mar 27-28, 1999; Jan & Dean (Box 78)
    - Show #99-14/895, Apr 3-4, 1999; modern folk (Box 78)
    - Show #99-15/896, Apr 10-11, 1999; Paul McCartney (Box 78)
    - Show #99-16/897, Apr 17-18, 1999; Lesley Gore (Box 78)
    - Show #99-17/898, Apr 24-25, 1999; Grass Roots (Box 78)
    - Show #99-18/899, May 1-2, 1999; Marvin Gaye (Box 78)
    - Show #99-19/900, May 8-9, 1999; Four Seasons (Box 78)
    - Show #99-20/901, May 15-16, 1999; Roy Orbison (Box 79)
    - Show #99-21/902, May 22-23, 1999; Beach Boys (Box 79)
    - Show #99-22/903, May 29-30, 1999; Petula Clark (Box 79)
    - Show #99-23/904, Jun 5-6, 1999; The Hollies (Box 79)
    - Show #99-24/905, Jun 12-13, 1999; Aretha Franklin (Box 79)
    - Show #99-25/906, Jun 19-20, 1999; Simon & Garfunkel (Box 79)
    - Show #99-26/907, Jun 26-27, 1999; Temptations (Box 79)
    - Show #99-27/908, Jul 3-4, 1999; Hal Blaine (Box 79)
    - Show #99-28/909, Jul 10-11, 1999; Sam Cooke (Box 79)
    - Show #99-29/910, Jul 17-18, 1999; Johnny Rivers (Box 79)
    - Show #99-30/911, Jul 24-25, 1999; Beatles (Box 80)
    - Show #99-31/912, Jul 31-Aug 1, 1999; Monkees (Box 80)
    - Show #99-32/913, Aug 7-8, 1999; Motown Music (Box 80)
    - Show #99-33/914, Aug 14-15, 1999; Elvis Presley (Box 80)
    - Show #99-34/915, Aug 21-22, 1999; Ray Charles (Box 80)
    - Show #99-35/916, Aug 28-29, 1999; The Beatles (Box 80)
    - Show #99-36/917, Sep 4-5, 1999; Rip Chords (Box 80)
    - Show #99-37/918, Sep 11-12, 1999; Neil Sedaka (Box 80)
    - Show #99-38/919, Sep 18-19, 1999; Jackie Wilson (Box 80)
    - Show #99-39/920, Sep 25-26, 1999; Rascals (Box 80)
    - Show #99-40/921, Oct 2-3, 1999; The Searchers (Box 80)
    - Show #99-41/922, Oct 9-10, 1999; The Spinners (Box 80)
    - Show #99-42/923, Oct 16-17, 1999; Herman’s Hermits (Box 81)
    - Show #99-43/924, Oct 23-24, 1999; Drifters (Box 81)
    - Show #99-44/925, Oct 30-31, 1999; Association (Box 81)
    - Show #99-45/926, Nov 6-7, 1999; Four Tops (Box 81)
    - Show #99-46/927, Nov 13-14, 1999; Salute to Dance (Box 81)
    - Show #99-47/928, Nov 20-21, 1999; Rick Nelson (Box 81)
    - Show #99-48/929, Nov 27-28, 1999; The Rivingtons (Box 81)
    - Show #99-49/930, Dec 4-5, 1999; John Lennon (Box 81)
    - Show #99-50/931, Dec 11-12, 1999; Dave Clark Five (Box 81)
    - Show #99-51/932, Dec 18-19, 1999; RRR Christmas Show (Box 81)
    - Show #99-52/933, Dec 25-26, 1999; Neil Diamond (Box 81)
    - Show #00-01/934, Jan 1-2, 2000; Little Richard (Box 82)
    - Show #00-02/935, Jan 8-9, 2000; Jay & the Americans (Box 82)
    - Show #00-03/936, Jan 15-16, 2000; Roy Orbison (Box 82)
    - Show #00-04/937, Jan 22-23, 2000; Dion (Box 82)
    - Show #00-05/938, Jan 29-30, 2000; George Harrison (Box 82)
    - Show #00-06/939, Feb 5-6, 2000; Martha & the Vandellas (Box 82)
    - Show #00-07/940, Feb 12-13, 2000; Hollies (Box 82)
    - Show #00-08/941, Feb 19-20, 2000; Tommy James & the Shondells (Box 82)
    - Show #00-09/942, Feb 26-27, 2000; Sly & the family Stone (Box 82)
    - Show #00-10/943, Mar 4-5, 2000; Mary Wellsfirst page says "00/10 & 00/11" (Box 82)
    - Show #00-11/944, Mar 11-12, 2000; Three Dog Night (Box 82)
    - Show #00-12/945, Mar 18-19, 2000; Bobby Darin (Box 82)
    - Show #00-13/946, Mar 25-26, 2000; O'Jays (Box 82)
    - Show #00-14/947, Apr 1-2, 2000; Lovin’ Spoonful (Box 83)
    - Show #00-15/948, Apr 8-9, 2000; Jerry Butler (Box 83)
    - Show #00-16/949, Apr 17-18, 2000; Paul McCartney (Box 83)
    - Show #00-17/950, Apr 24-25, 2000; Del Shannon (Box 83)
    - Show #00-18/951, Apr 29-30, 2000; Supremes (Box 83)
    - Show #00-19/952, May 6-7, 2000; Jan & Dean (Box 83)
    - Show #00-20/953, May 13-14, 2000; Chuck Berry (Box 83)
    - Show #00-21/954, May 20-21, 2000; Salute to Phil Spector (Box 83)
    - Show #00-22/955, May 27-28, 2000; Beach Boys (Box 83)
    - Show #00-23/956, Jun 3-4, 2000; Petula Clark (Box 83)
    - Show #00-24/957, Jun 10-11, 2000; Temptations (Box 83)
    - Show #00-25/958, Jun 17-18, 2000; Love Song Special (Box 84)
    - Show #00-26/959, Jun 24-25, 2000; Johnny Rivers (Box 84)
    - Show #00-27/960, Jul 1-2, 2000; All American Hits (Box 84)
    - Show #00-28/961, Jul 8-9, 2000; Bobby Vee (Box 84)
    - Show #00-29/962, Jul 17-18, 2000; Miracles (Box 84)
    - Show #00-30/963, Jul 22-23, 2000; Lesley Gore (Box 84)
    - Show #00-31/964 [not in collection], Jul 29-30, 2000; Monkees
    - Show #00-32/965, Aug 5-6, 2000; Fifth Dimension (Box 84)
    - Show #00-33/966, Aug 12-13, 2000; Rascals (Box 84)
    - Show #00-34/967, Aug 19-20, 2000; Salute to Vocal Groups (Box 84)
    - Show #00-35/968, Aug 26-27, 2000; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 84)
    - Show #00-36/969, Sep 2-3, 2000; Summer Beach Party3 pp only, rest missing' (Box 84)
    - Show #00-37/970, Sep 9-10, 2000; Ben E. King (Box 84)
    - Show #00-38/971, Sep 16-17, 2000; Mamas & the Papas (Box 84)
    - Show #00-39/972, Sep 23-24, 2000; Buddy Holly (Box 85)
    - Show #00-40/973, Sep 30-Oct 1, 2000; Herman’s Hermits (Box 85)
    - Show #00-41/974, Oct 7-8, 2000; Marvin Gaye (Box 85)
    - Show #00-42/975, Oct 14-15, 2000; Kinks (Box 85)
    - Show #00-43/976, Oct 21-22, 2000; Salute to Dance (Box 85)
    - Show #00-44/977, Oct 28-29, 2000; Duane Eddy (Box 85)
    - Show #00-45/978, Nov 4-5, 2000; Gene Pitney (Box 85)
    - Show #00-46/979, Nov 11-12, 2000; John Lennon (Box 85)
    - Show #00-47/980, Nov 18-19, 2000; Little Anthony & the Imperials (Box 85)
    - Show #00-48/981, Nov 25-26, 2000; Rick Nelson (Box 85)
    - Show #00-49/982, Dec 2-3, 2000; Four Tops (Box 85)
    - Show #00-50/983, Dec 9-10, 2000; Dave Clark Five (Box 86)
    - Show #00-51/984, Dec 16-17, 2000; Turtles (Box 86)
    - Show #00-52/985, Dec 23-24, 2000; RRR Christmas Show (Box 86)
    - Show #00-53/986, Dec 30-31, 2000; Neil Diamond (Box 86)
    - Show #01-01/987 to 02-25/1063 [not in collection], Jan 2001 - Jun 2002
    - Show #02-26/1064, Jun 29-30, 2002; Rascals (Box 86)
    - Show #02-27/1065, Jul 6-7, 2002; Beach Boys (Box 86)
    - Show #02-28/1066, Jul 13-14, 2002; Neil Diamond (Box 86)
    - Show #02-29/1067, Jul 20-21, 2002; O'Jays (Box 86)
    - Show #02-30/1068, Jul 27-28, 2002; Ray Charles (Box 86)
    - Show #02-31/1069, Aug 3-4, 2002; Lovin' Spoonful (Box 86)
    - Show #02-32/1070, Aug 10-11, 2002; Donovan (Box 86)
    - Show #02-33/1071, Aug 17-18, 2002; Miracles (Box 86)
    - Show #02-34/1072, Aug 24-25, 2002; Platters (Box 86)
    - Show #02-35/1073, Aug 31-Sep 1, 2002; Beach Party Blowout (Box 87)
    - Show #02-36/1074, Sep 7-8, 2002; John Lennon (Box 87)
    - Show #02-37/1075, Sep 14-15, 2002; Dance Hits special (Box 87)
    - Show #02-38/1076, Sep 21-22, 2002; Roy Orbison (Box 87)
    - Show #02-39/1077, Sep 28-29, 2002; Everly Brothers (Box 87)
    - Show #02-40/1078, Oct 5-6, 2002; Spinners (Box 87)
    - Show #02-41/1079, Oct 12-13, 2002; Superstars of Motown (Box 87)
    - Show #02-42/1080, Oct 19-20, 2002; Hollies (Box 87)
    - Show #02-43/1081, Oct 26-27, 2002; Stevie Wonder (Box 87)
    - Show #02-44/1082, Nov 2-3, 2002; Jerry Lee Lewisintro and song list only (Box 87)
    - Show #02-45/1083, Nov 9-10, 2002; Dave Clark Five (Box 87)
    - Show #02-46/1084, Nov 16-17, 2002; Drifters (Box 87)
    - Show #02-47/1085, Nov 23-24, 2002; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 87)
    - Show #02-48/1086, Nov 30-Dec 1, 2002; Sam Cooke (Box 87)
    - Show #02-49/1087, Dec 7-8, 2002; Paul McCartney (Box 87)
    - Show #02-50/1088, Dec 14-15, 2002; Aretha Franklin (Box 88)
    - Show #02-51/1089, Dec 21-22, 2002; George Harrison; outro and song list only (Box 88)
    - Show #02-52/1090, Dec 28-29, 2002; George Harrison (Box 88)
    - Show #03-01/1091, Jan 4-5, 2003; Singer-Songwriters special (Box 88)
    - Show #03-02/1092, Jan 11-12, 2003; Gladys Knight & the Pips (Box 88)
    - Show #03-03/1093, Jan 18-19, 2003; Chicago (Box 88)
    - Show #03-04/1094, Jan 25-26, 2003; Lesley Gore (Box 88)
    - Show #03-05/1095, Feb 1-2, 2003; Supremes (Box 88)
    - Show #03-06/1096, Feb 8-9, 2003; Dion (of Dion and the Belmonts) (Box 88)
    - Show #03-07/1097, Feb 15-16, 2003; Turtles (Box 88)
    - Show #03-08/1098, Feb 22-23, 2003; Mary Wells (Box 88)
    - Show #03-09/1099, Mar 1-2, 2003; English Invasion special (Box 88)
    - Show #03-10/1100, Mar 8-9, 2003; Johnny Rivers (Box 88)
    - Show #03-11/1101, Mar 15-16, 2003; The Association (Box 88)
    - Show #03-12/1102, Mar 22-23, 2003; Bee Gees (Box 88)
    - Show #03-13/1103, Mar 29-30, 2003; Jackie Wilson (Box 88)
    - Show #03-14/1104, Apr 5-6, 2003; Simon and Garfunkel (Box 89)
    - Show #03-15/1105, Apr 12-13, 2003; Three Dog Night (Box 89)
    - Show #03-16/1106, Apr 19-20, 2003; Guess Who (Box 89)
    - Show #03-17/1107, Apr 26-27, 2003; Kinks (Box 89)
    - Show #03-18/1108, May 3-4, 2003; Fifth Dimension (Box 89)
    - Show #03-19/1109, May 10-11, 2003; Beatles (Box 89)
    - Show #03-20/1110, May 17-18, 2003; Spinners (Box 89)
    - Show #03-21/1111, May 24-25, 2003; Beach Boys (Box 89)
    - Show #03-22/1112, May 31-Jun 1, 2003; Elton John (Box 89)
    - Show #03-23/1113, Jun 7-8, 2003; Rascals (Box 89)
    - Show #03-24/1114, Jun 14-15, 2003; Monterey Pop Festival 1967 (Box 89)
    - Show #03-25/1115, Jun 21-22, 2003; Jim Croce (Box 89)
    - Show #03-26/1116, Jun 28-29, 2003; Monkees (Box 89)
    - Show #03-27/1117, Jul 5-6, 2003; July 4th All American Hits special (Box 89)
    - Show #03-28/1118, Jul 12-13, 2003; Herman’s Hermits (Box 90)
    - Show #03-29/1119, Jul 19-20, 2003; Smokey Robinson and the Miracles (Box 90)
    - Show #03-30/1120, Jul 26-27, 2003; Doors/Linda Ronstadt (Box 90)
    - Show #03-31/1121, Aug 2-3, 2003; Stevie Wonder (Box 90)
    - Show #03-32/1122, Aug 9-10, 2003; Dave Clark Five (Box 90)
    - Show #03-33/1123, Aug 16-17, 2003; Hollies (Box 90)
    - Show #03-34/1124, Aug 23-24, 2003; Neil Diamond (Box 90)
    - Show #03-35/1125, Aug 30-31, 2003; Superstars of Motown (Box 90)
    - Show #03-36/1126, Sep 6-7, 2003; Chiffons (Box 90)
    - Show #03-37/1127, Sep 13-14, 2003; Solo Male Performers special (Box 90)
    - Show #03-38/1128, Sep 20-21, 2003; Supremes (Box 90)
    - Show #03-39/1129, Sep 27-28, 2003; Chicago Bands special (Box 90)
    - Show #03-40/1130, Oct 4-5, 2003; John Lennon (Box 90)
    - Show #03-41/1131, Oct 11-12, 2003; Petula Clark (Box 90)
    - Show #03-42/1132, Oct 18-19, 2003; Marvin Gaye (Box 90)
    - Show #03-43/1133, Oct 25-26, 2003; Four Seasons (Box 91)
    - Show #03-44/1134, Nov 1-2, 2003; Isley Brothers (Box 91)
    - Show #03-45/1135, Nov 8-9, 2003; Mamas and the Papas (Box 91)
    - Show #03-46/1136, Nov 15-16, 2003; Four Tops (Box 91)
    - Show #03-47/1137, Nov 22-23, 2003; Top Teen Idols special (Box 91)
    - Show #03-48/1138, Nov 29-30, 2003; Dusty Springfield (Box 91)
    - Show #03-49/1139, Dec 6-7, 2003; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 91)
    - Show #03-50/1140, Dec 13-14, 2003; Temptations (Box 91)
    - Show #03-51/1141, Dec 20-21, 2003; George Harrison? Christmas show?later pages have episode #1037, date of Dec 19-20, 2001 (Box 91)
    - Show #03-52/1142, Dec 27-28, 2003; George Harrison (Box 91)
    - Show #04-01/1143, Jan 3-4, 2004; Number One Hits of Rock Era (Box 91)
    - Show #04-02/1144, Jan 10-11, 2004; Johnny Rivers (Box 91)
    - Show #04-03/1145, Jan 17-18, 2004; Singer-Songwriters special (Box 91)
    - Show #04-04/1146, Jan 24-25, 2004; Turtles (Box 91)
    - Show #04-05/1147, Jan 31-Feb 1, 2004; Rock and Roll A-Through-Z (Box 91)
    - Show #04-06/1148, Feb 7-8, 2004; Beatlesalso has handwritten date of Feb 5-6, 2005 (Box 92)
    - Show #04-07/1149, Feb 14-15, 2004; Romance specialalso has handwritten date of Feb 12-13, 2005 (Box 92)
    - Show #04-08/1150, Feb 21-22, 2004; Grass Rootsalso has handwritten date of Feb 19-20, 2005 (Box 92)
    - Show #04-09/1151, Feb 28-29, 2004; Number 2's specialalso has handwritten date of Feb 26-27, 2005 (Box 92)
    - Show #04-10/1152, Mar 6-7, 2004; English Invasion specialalso has handwritten date of Mar 5-6, 2005 (Box 92)
    - Show #04-11/1153, Mar 13-14, 2004; Lovin' Spoonful (Box 92)
    - Show #04-12/1154, Mar 20-21, 2004; Tommy James and the Shondells (Box 92)
    - Show #04-13/1155, Mar 27-28, 2004; Female Solo Artists special (Box 92)
    - Show #04-14/1156, Apr 3-4, 2004; O'Jays (Box 92)
    - Show #04-15/1157, Apr 10-11, 2004; Martha and the Vandellas (Box 92)
    - Show #04-16/1158, Apr 17-18 2004; Dion and the Belmonts (Box 92)
    - Show #04-17/1159, Apr 24-25, 2004; The Buckinghams (Box 92)
    - Show #04-18/1160, May 1-2, 2004; Jan and Dean (Box 92)
    - Show #04-19/1161, May 8-9, 2004; The Drifters (Box 92)
    - Show #04-20/1162, May 15-16, 2004; The Zombiesalso has handwritten date of May 14-15, 2005 (Box 92)
    - Show #04-21/1163, May 22-23, 2004; Paul Revere (Box 93)
    - Show #04-22/1164, May 29-30, 2004; Memorial Day special (Box 93)
    - Show #04-23/1165, Jun 5-6, 2004; Phil Spectoralso has handwritten date of Jun 4-5, 2005; handwritten on second page is "USMS 04-22" (Box 93)
    - Show #04-24/1166, Jun 12-13, 2004; Sly and the Family Stone (Box 93)
    - Show #04-25/1167, Jun 19-20, 2004; Gary Lewis and the Playboysalso has handwritten date of Jun 18-19, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-26/1168, Jun 26-27, 2004; The Twist [the dance, not a group]also has handwritten date of Jun 25-26, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-27/1169, Jul 3-4, 2004; The Beach Boysalso has handwritten date of Jul 2-3, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-28/1170, Jul 10-11, 2004; Creedence Clearwater Revival (Box 93)
    - Show #04-29/1171, Jul 17-18, 2004; Gladys Knight and the Pipsalso has handwritten date of Jul 16-17, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-30/1172, Jul 24-25, 2004; The Rascalsalso has handwritten date of Jul 23-24, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-31/1173, Jul 31-Aug 1, 2004; Saviors of Soul specialalso has handwritten date of Jul 30-31, 2005 (Box 93)
    - Show #04-32/1174, Aug 7-8, 2004; The Kinksalso has handwritten date of Aug 6-7, 2005 (Box 93)